Levon Khosrovyan

Yerevan, Yerevan, Armenia



levonkhosrovyan@gmail.com



+37494858437



linkedin.com/in/levon-khosrovyan-aa8401205

Summary

Experienced SAS Programmer with a demonstrated history of SAS programming experience covering all aspects of SAS processes – analysis, design, testing and validating, including advanced statistical methodologies applied in Pharmaceutical and Biotech industries (Clinical Environment). Rich background in general linear models, categorical data analysis, survival analysis, multivariate analysis, design of experiments, longitudinal data analysis, randomized trial designs and survey design and analysis, as well as creating SAS datasets, macro definitions, debugging programs, and documentation. Possess solid ability in integrating programing skills, adapting to new applications and platforms, and converting data from complex clinical systems. Experienced in working on multiple protocols and/or drug compounds at a time, able to utilize CDISC for verifying compliance of datasets with CDISC standards and electronic submissions, generate analysis datasets based on the Data Definition Tables (DDT) and in accordance to the CDISC standard, use SDTM model (3.1.1)/ ADAM for domain creation and CDISC compliant analysis datasets, render support in generating analysis data sets and creating specified structure of TLFs through creating Macros and macro variables, facilitate the modification and development of existing SAS programs as well as accountable for the creation of new programs using SAS Macros as well as perform extensive QC (Quality Check) and analysis in reviewing other team members work as well as render primary support and assistance in data validation and data cleaning in all phases of Clinical studies.

Experience



Statistical Programmer 2

Syneos Health Aug 2022 - Present (9 months)

Statistical Programmer

Axiom Real-Time Metrics Aug 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Clinical SAS Programmer

HydraLab LLC Apr 2018 - Aug 2021 (3 years 5 months)

Student Employee

HydraLab LLC Oct 2017 - Apr 2018 (7 months) SAS Statistical Programming courses

Education



🚞 Yerevan State University

Master's degree, Informatics and Applied Mathematics Sep 2015 - Jun 2017

math and the state University

Bachelor's degree, Tourism and Travel Services Management Sep 2009 - Jun 2013

Licenses & Certifications

- SAS® Programming SAS
- Doing More with SAS® Programming SAS
- Practical SAS® Programming and Certification Review SAS
- Practical SAS® Programming and Certification Review SAS
- Practicing for the SAS Programming Certification Exam SAS
- Structured Query Language (SQL) using SAS SAS
- SAS Macro Language SAS
- Advanced SAS Programming Techniques SAS
- GCP for Clinical Investigations of Devices CITI Program Issued Sep 2021 Expires Sep 2022 45009548
- SAS Programmer Specialization Coursera
 Y27MSYSUHW7T
- SAS Advanced Programmer Specialization Coursera
 MGA96HH68KXZ
- Getting Started with SAS Programming Coursera
 B7VEJ5V3X83U
- Doing More with SAS Programming Coursera
 L67RANWHJKSA

- Structured Query Language (SQL) using SAS (with Honors) Coursera YU8QBBURHD2E
- SAS Macro Language (with Honors) Coursera
 GSAD9J7H2XPV
- Preparing for the SAS Programming Certification Exam Coursera
 9UW9YU5BPK69
- Advanced SAS Programming Techniques Coursera
 9JLLUQLWZDXW
- Practicing for the SAS Programming Certification Exam Coursera
 RELPNYVX8F59
- GCP for Clinical Trials with Investigational Drugs and Biologics (ICH Focus) CITI Program
 Issued Oct 2021 Expires Oct 2022
 45523468
- GCP for Clinical Investigations of Devices CITI Program
 Issued Jan 2022 Expires Jan 2023
 46742056
- GCP for Clinical Trials with Investigational Drugs and Biologics (ICH Focus) CITI Program
 Issued Jan 2022 Expires Jan 2023
 46742116

Skills

SAS (Programming Language) • SAS/Macro • SAS/SQL • SAS/Advanced • SAS Programming • SAS Macros • Data Analysis • Data Analytics • Data Science • Study Data Tabulation Model (SDTM)